Hawthorne Studies Records on Microfilm. 5856 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Material from Box 15: Folders1-14; Box 16: Folders 1-12; Box 17: Folders 1-10 (Reel 7)
  - Articles on and outlines of articles on research studies in employee effectiveness and industrial relations, 1929; 32 (Reel 7)
    Box 17: Folder 8: Test studies in industrial research at Hawthorne by G. A. Pennock; A plan for improving employee relations on the basis of data obtained from employees by M. L. Putnam; and Changes in industry by Elton Mayo.
  - A plan for improving employee relations., 1929; 33 (Reel 7)
    Box 17: Folder 9
- Negative copy of Reel 1. (Reel 8)
- Negative copy of Reel 2. (Reel 9)
- Negative copy of Reel 3. (Reel 10)
- Negative copy of Reel 4. (Reel 11)
- Negative copy of Reel 5. (Reel 12)
- Negative copy of Reel 6. (Reel 13)
- Negative copy of Reel 7. (Reel 14)